loadimpact.com 2019-04-23

# Privacy Policy | Load Impact

Information on what personal data LoadImpact collects and how we process it

##  Overview 

This Privacy Policy explains how LoadImpact collects, uses and shares your “Personal Information” – information that identifies, relates to, describes or is capable of being associated with you as a particular individual, such as your name, address, email address or telephone number – and other data through your use of any of LoadImpact’s websites, services or application programming interfaces (APIs).

Your use of the LoadImpact’s service is subject to this Privacy Policy in effect at the time of your use. LoadImpact reserves the right to update and change this Privacy Policy, inform and ask you to accept the changes from time to time.

##  Collection of personal information 

When you register for a LoadImpact account, your are required to provide email contact information for us to be able to send you on-boarding information and verify your account. Other information such as your name, company name or affiliation, email address and location are optional to your discretion.

For subscriptions of premium accounts, we may collect additional personal information such as credit card number and billing address that is required to process the payment transaction. LoadImpact has no knowledge about your full credit card number as this resides with our payment gateway providers.

LoadImpact on such occassion may collect information about your transactions with us and/or with our business partners. This information might include information necessary to process payments, such as billing information and your credit card number.

##  Use of personal information 

LoadImpact uses the Personal Information it collects for the following general purposes:

  * Products and services provision
  * Billing, identification and authentication
  * Improvement of services
  * Contact
  * Research
  * Analytics and reporting
  * Abuse prevention

You will automatically be subscribed to receive optional email messages, you may choose to unsubscribe at anytime. In addition to these optional email messages, LoadImpact may contact you via email with transactional or relationship messages such as account status messages, security updates or notifications of changes in the terms of your account. These types of transactional or relationship email messages are not optional.

LoadImpact may automatically receive and record information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, cookies and the pages you request.

##  Sharing of personal information 

LoadImpact does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you’ve requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

  * We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, violations of LoadImpact’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. An example of such illegal activity is using LoadImpact to execute a denial of service (DDOS) attack on a website or application not legally owned or managed by the user.

  * We provide the information to trusted partners such as performance engineers, testing professionals, or consultants who work with or on behalf of LoadImpact under confidentiality agreements.

  * As we continue to operate, we may merge or be acquired by another entity. In this event, we may transfer information about you. LoadImpact will notify you before any information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

##  Cookies 

A “cookie” is a small amount of data, which typically includes an anonymous unique identifier, which is sent to your browser and stored on your computer’s hard drive when you view a webpage, an advertisement, a video or other types of content. You can configure your browser to accept all cookies, reject all cookies or notify you when a cookie is set. If you reject all cookies, or specifically reject cookies set by LoadImpact, you may not be able to take full advantage of features of the LoadImpact Service that require you to be signed in to your account or otherwise identify yourself.

LoadImpact uses cookies for a number of purposes, including to:

  * Identify you as an account holder. Require you to re-enter your password after a certain period of time has elapsed to protect you against others accidentally accessing your account contents.
  * Keep track of preferences you specify while you are using LoadImpact’s Sites, Services and Software.
  * Retargeting

##### **Retargeting**

LoadImpact uses cookies to capture anonymous browsing information for purposes of website optimization, measurement, and online marketing. You can opt out of Google’s use of cookies by visiting [Google’s ads settings](http://www.google.com/settings/ads?) and [Adroll’s ad settings](http://info.evidon.com/pub_info/573?v=1&nt=1&nw=false). You may also choose to delete your cookies through your browser’s privacy settings.

LoadImpact collects data about your activities that does not personally or directly identify you when you visit our website. This information may include the content you view, the date and time that you view this content, the products you purchase, or your location information associated with your IP address.

We use the information we collect to serve you more relevant advertisements (referred to as “Retargeting”).

##  Data transmission and storage 

Since no data transmitted over the internet can be 100% secure, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us. However, we make every effort to secure your data by working closely with trusted third party vendors and hosting partners needed to run the LoadImpact Service. Where possible, we seek to obtain confidentiality agreements with these providers that are consistent with this Privacy Policy and that limit their use or disclosure of your Personal Information.

##  Questions 

Any questions about this Privacy Policy should be addressed to [support@loadimpact.com](mailto:support@loadimpact.com).

**Last updated February  02, 2018.**
